<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Beautiful Place</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="getting_data">Getting data</string>
    <string name="place_name">Place Name</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="email">fahrizalmursalin06@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="name">Fachrizal A. Z. Mursalin</string>
    <string name="maldives_description">
        Unrivalled luxury, stunning white-sand beaches and an amazing underwater world make
        Maldives an obvious choice for a true holiday of a lifetime. Maldives is
        home to perhaps the best beaches in the world; they are on almost every one of
        the country nearly 1200 islands and are so consistently perfect that its hard not to
        become blase about them. While some beaches may boast softer granules than others, the basic
        fact remains: you wont find consistently whiter-than-white powder sand and luminous
        cyan-blue water like this anywhere else on earth. This fact alone is enough to bring well
        over a million people a year to this tiny, remote and otherwise little-known Indian Ocean paradise. 
        Every resort in Maldives is its own private island, and with over 100 to choose from the only problem 
        is selecting where you want to stay. At the top end, the worlds most exclusive hotel brands compete 
        with each other to attain ever-greater heights of luxury, from personal butlers and private lap pools 
        to in-room massages and pillow menus. Its not surprising that honeymooners and those seeking a 
        glamorous tropical getaway have long had the country at the very top of their wish lists. But there is
        also plenty of choice beyond the five- and six-star resorts.
    </string>
    <string name="bora_bora_description">
        Bora Bora (French: Bora-Bora; Tahitian: Pora Pora) is a 30.55 km2 (12 sq mi) island group in the
        Leeward group in the western part of the Society Islands of French Polynesia, an overseas
        collectivity of the French Republic in the Pacific Ocean. The main island, located about 230
        kilometres (143 miles) northwest of Papeete, is surrounded by a lagoon and a barrier reef.
        In the center of the island are the remnants of an extinct volcano rising to two peaks,
        Mount Pahia and Mount Otemanu, the highest point at 727 metres (2,385 feet). It is part of
        the commune of Bora-Bora, which also includes the atoll of Tūpai.
        Bora Bora is a major international tourist destination,
        famous for its aqua-centric luxury resorts. The major settlement,
        Vaitape, is on the western side of the main island, opposite the main channel
        into the lagoon. Produce of the island is mostly limited to what can be obtained from the
        sea and the plentiful coconut trees, which were historically of economic importance for copra.
    </string>
    <string name="mount_bromo_description">
        Mount Bromo (Indonesian: Gunung Bromo), is an active volcano and part of the Tengger massif,
        in East Java, Indonesia. The volcano belongs to the Bromo Tengger Semeru National Park.
        The name of Bromo derived from Javanese pronunciation of Brahma, the Hindu creator god. It
        is a major pilgrimage centre for Hindus in Indonesia, particularly Tenggerese Hindus.They make
        pilgrimage during the Yadnya Kasada. Mount Bromo sits in the middle of a plain called the
        "Sea of Sand" (Javanese: Segara Wedi or Indonesian: Lautan Pasir), a
        protected nature reserve since 1919. The typical way to visit Mount Bromo
        is from the nearby mountain village of Cemoro Lawang. From there it is possible
        to walk to the volcano in about 45 minutes, but it is also possible to take an organised
        jeep tour, which includes a stop at the viewpoint on Mount Penanjakan (2,770 m or 9,088 ft)
        (Indonesian: Gunung Penanjakan). The viewpoint on Mount Penanjakan can also be reached on
        foot in about two hours. Depending on the degree of volcanic activity,
        the Indonesian Centre for Volcanology and Disaster Hazard Mitigation sometimes
        issues warnings against visiting Mount Bromo.
    </string>
    <string name="colosseum_description">
        The Colosseum or Coliseum, also known as the Flavian Amphitheatre
        (Latin: Amphitheatrum Flavium; Italian: Anfiteatro Flavio or Colosseo, is an oval
        amphitheatre in the centre of the city of Rome, Italy. Built of travertine limestone,
        tuff (volcanic rock), and brick-faced concrete, it was the largest amphitheatre ever
        built at the time and held 50,000 spectators. The Colosseum is situated just east of the
        Roman Forum. Construction began under the emperor Vespasian in AD 72 and was completed
        in AD 80 under his successor and heir, Titus. Further modifications were made during the
        reign of Domitian (81–96). These three emperors are known as the Flavian dynasty, and
        the amphitheatre was named in Latin for its association with their family name (Flavius).
        The Colosseum could hold an estimated 50,000 to 80,000 spectators during phases of its
        various renovations over the centuries,having an average audience of some 65,000;
        it was used for gladiatorial contests and public spectacles such as mock sea battles
        (for only a short time as the hypogeum was soon filled in with mechanisms to support the
        other activities), animal hunts, executions, re-enactments of famous battles, and dramas
        based on Classical mythology. The building ceased to be used for entertainment in the early
        medieval era. It was later reused for such purposes as housing, workshops, quarters for a
        religious order, a fortress, a quarry, and a Christian shrine.
        Although substantially ruined because of earthquakes, thieves, and stone-robbers,
        the Colosseum is still an iconic symbol of Imperial Rome and is listed as one of the
        New7Wonders of the World. It is one of Romes most popular tourist attractions and also
        has links to the Roman Catholic Church, as each Good Friday the Pope leads a torchlit "Way
        of the Cross" procession that starts in the area around the Colosseum. In 2018, it was
        the most popular tourist attraction in the world, with 7.4 million visitors.
    </string>
    <string name="labuan_bajo_description">
        Labuan Bajo is the gateway for trips across the nearby Komodo National Park to Komodo
        Island and Rinca Island, both home to the famous Komodo dragons. There are numerous
        snorkling points in the islands close to Labuan Bajo. Kanawa and Seraya Islands, for
        example, offer good diving and snorkeling sites. Currents can be strong at some sites
        however so care is needed. Every evening at Kalong Island, to the south of Labuan
        Bajo, thousands of flying fox bats (known as burung kalong in Indonesian) provide an
        amazing display. Around dusk the bats rise up from the mangroves around Kalong Island
        and within a few minutes, a column begins to form as thousands of bats begin to traverse
        across to the main island of Flores to the east. More and more bats join the column for
        perhaps the next 30 mins or so. The column soon forms into a remarkable trail across the sky
        stretching for miles as the bats fly east to Flores to search for food in the nearby forests.
    </string>
    <string name="eiffel_tower_description">
        The Eiffel Tower French: tour Eiffel (About this soundlisten)) is
        a wrought-iron lattice tower on the Champ de Mars in Paris, France.
        It is named after the engineer Gustave Eiffel, whose company designed and built the tower.
        Constructed from 1887 to 1889 as the entrance to the 1889 Worlds
        Fair, it was initially criticised by some of Frances leading artists
        and intellectuals for its design, but it has become a global cultural icon of France and one
        of the most recognisable structures in the world. The Eiffel Tower is the most-visited paid
        monument in the world; 6.91 million people ascended it in 2015. The tower is 324
        metres (1,063 ft) tall, about the same height as an 81-storey building, and the tallest structure
        in Paris. Its base is square, measuring 125 metres (410 ft) on each side. During its construction,
        the Eiffel Tower surpassed the Washington Monument to become the tallest man-made structure in the
        world, a title it held for 41 years until the Chrysler Building in New York City was finished in
        1930. It was the first structure to reach a height of 300 metres. Due to the addition of a
        broadcasting aerial at the top of the tower in 1957, it is now taller than the Chrysler Building
        by 5.2 metres (17 ft). Excluding transmitters, the Eiffel Tower is the second tallest free-standing
        structure in France after the Millau Viaduct.
    </string>
    <string name="santorini_description">
        Santorini , officially Thira (Greek: and classic Greek Thera (English pronunciation),
        is an island in the southern Aegean Sea, about 200 km (120 mi) southeast of Greeces
        mainland. It is the largest island of a small, circular archipelago, which bears the
        same name and is the remnant of a volcanic caldera. It forms the southernmost member of
        the Cyclades group of islands, with an area of approximately 73 km2 (28 sq mi) and a 2011
        census population of 15,550. The municipality of Santorini includes the inhabited islands of
        Santorini and Therasia, as well as the uninhabited islands of Nea Kameni, Palaia Kameni,
        Aspronisi and Christiana. The total land area is 90.623 km2 (34.990 sq mi). Santorini
        is part of the Thira regional unit. The island was the site of one of the
        largest volcanic eruptions in recorded history: the Minoan eruption (sometimes
        called the Thera eruption), which occurred about 3,600 years ago at the height of
        the Minoan civilization. The eruption left a large caldera surrounded by volcanic
        ash deposits hundreds of metres deep. It may have led indirectly to the collapse of the
        Minoan civilization on the island of Crete, 110 km (68 mi) to the south, through a gigantic
        tsunami. Another popular theory holds that the Thera eruption is the source of the legend of Atlantis.
        It is the most active volcanic centre in the South Aegean Volcanic Arc, though what remains today
        is chiefly a water-filled caldera. The volcanic arc is approximately 500 km (310 mi)
        long and 20 to 40 km (12 to 25 mi) wide. The region first became volcanically active around 3–4
        million years ago[citation needed], though volcanism on Thera began around 2 million years ago
        with the extrusion of dacitic lavas from vents around Akrotiri.
    </string>
    <string name="mount_fuji_description">
        Mount Fuji (富士山 Fujisan, IPA:  (About this soundlisten)), 
        located on Honshū, is the highest volcano in Japan at 3,776.24 m (12,389 ft), 
        2nd-highest volcano of an island in Asia (after Mount Kerinci in Sumatra), and 
        7th-highest peak of an island in the world. It is an active stratovolcano that last erupted
        in 1707–1708. Mount Fuji lies about 100 kilometers (60 mi) south-west of Tokyo, and can be
        seen from there on a clear day. Mount Fujis exceptionally symmetrical cone, which is snow-capped 
        for about 5 months a year, is commonly used as a symbol of Japan and it is frequently depicted in 
        art and photographs, as well as visited by sightseers and climbers.
        Mount Fuji is one of Japans "Three Holy Mountains" along with Mount 
        Tate and Mount Haku. It is also a Special Place of Scenic Beauty and one of 
        Japans Historic Sites. It was added to the World Heritage List as a Cultural
        Site on June 22, 2013. According to UNESCO, Mount Fuji has
        "inspired artists and poets and been the object of pilgrimage for centuries".
        UNESCO recognizes 25 sites of
        cultural interest within the Mount Fuji locality. These 25 locations include the mountain 
        and the Shinto shrine, Fujisan Hongū Sengen Taisha, as well as the Buddhist Taisekiji Head 
        Temple founded in 1290, later depicted by Japanese ukiyo-e artist Katsushika Hokusai.
    </string>
    <string name="great_wall_description">
        The Great Wall of China (Chinese: 萬里長城; pinyin: Wànlǐ Chángchéng) is the collective name
        of a series of fortification systems generally built across the historical northern borders
        of China to protect and consolidate territories of Chinese states and empires against various
        nomadic groups of the steppe and their polities. Several walls were being built from as early
        as the 7th century BC by ancient Chinese states; selective stretches were later joined together
        by Qin Shi Huang (220–206 BC), the first Emperor of China. Little of the Qin wall remains.
        Later on, many successive dynasties have built and maintained multiple stretches of border walls.
        The most well-known sections of the wall were built by the Ming dynasty (1368–1644).
        Apart from defense, other purposes of the Great Wall have included border controls,
        allowing the imposition of duties on goods transported along the Silk Road, regulation
        or encouragement of trade and the control of immigration and emigration. Furthermore,
        the defensive characteristics of the Great Wall were enhanced by the construction of
        watch towers, troop barracks, garrison stations, signaling capabilities through the means
        of smoke or fire, and the fact that the path of the Great Wall also served as a transportation corridor.
    </string>
    <string name="jeju_island">
        From April 3, 1948 to May 1949, the South Korean government conducted an anticommunist
        campaign to suppress an attempted uprising on the island. The main cause for the
        rebellion was the election scheduled for May 10, 1948, designed by the United Nations Temporary
        Commission on Korea (UNTCOK) to create a new government for all of Korea. The elections were only
        planned for the south of the country, the half of the peninsula under UNTCOK control. Fearing
        that the elections would further reinforce division, guerrilla fighters for the South Korean
        Labor party (SKLP) reacted violently, attacking local police and rightist youth groups stationed
        on Jeju Island. Atrocities were committed by both sides, but those
        by South Korean government forces are the best-documented. On one occasion, American soldiers
        discovered the bodies of 97 people who had been killed by government forces. On another,
        American soldiers encountered police who were executing 76 villagers. Between 40,000 and 60,000
        people died as a result of the rebellion, or up to 25% of the island’s total population. Some
        40,000 others fled to Japan to escape the fighting. In the decades after the uprising,
        memory of the event was suppressed by the government through strict punishment. However, in 2006,
        the Korean government apologized for its role in the killings and promised reparations. As
        of 2010, these had not been paid. In 2008, bodies of victims of a massacre
        were discovered in a mass grave near Jeju International Airport.
    </string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="source_wikipedia">Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
</resources>
